A Line of Fire is a action, thriller film directed by Matt Shapira.
After working as a secret agent in the FBI for ten years, Jack 'Cash' Conry left it all
behind after his wife passed in order to dedicate himself to his two daughters.
Despite a fulfilling life at home, Cash misses the chance to make an
impact and has been considering a return to the force.
The decision is made for him when his old partner’s niece Jamie calls him for help,
launching Cash right back into a world of danger, corruption and intrigue.
Jack 'Cash' Conry, played by David A.R. White.
Javier Cardona, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Jamie, played by Katrina Bowden.
Josef Amali, played by Jason Patric.
Bron, played by Scott Baio.
Nacho, played by Gabriel 'G-Rod' Rodriguez.
In the Line of Fire is a 1993 American political action thriller film directed by
Wolfgang Petersen and starring Clint Eastwood, John Malkovich and Rene Russo.
Written by Jeff Maguire, the film is about a disillusioned and obsessed former CIA agent who plans to
assassinate the President of the United States and the Secret Service agent who is tracking him.
Eastwood's character is the sole remaining active-duty Secret
Service agent from the detail that was guarding John F.
Kennedy in Dallas, Texas at the time of his assassination in 1963.
The film also stars Dylan McDermott, Gary Cole, John
Mahoney, and Fred Dalton Thompson.
In the Line of Fire was co-produced by Columbia Pictures and Castle
Rock Entertainment, with Columbia handling distribution.
The film was a critical and commercial success.
It grossed $187 million against a $40 million production budget and
earned three nominations at the 66th Academy Awards.
The tone is intense.